knock knock who's there who's there
ouch o achoo sounds like you have a cold
let me heal you up
trust me everyone with Bastion on our
side this is going to go great
[Music]
who the boss I thought he was decorative
just make sure you're shooting them and
not me please
looks like a pile of outdated junk to me
oh well doomed well I'm happy to have
you
Genji remember the time you tripped over
your sword in training
wish I was there
oh that sounds like him
is that true no way
some Ninja
really what
it only happened once once was enough
chip I need you to make me something
else a robot guard dog for me dirt
Garden maybe it can fly you decide a
suit of armor right but one that shouts
my name I need a slot bucket that's
bulletproof and don't you dare ask why a
grenade launcher with one trigger three
barrels paint glitter and nails
fine
fine Peter Piper picked a pip no Peter
Piper picked up are you people always
this loud don't lump Us in with him he's
not with us he's not with us he's uh not
with us
we should do a concert together oh what
do you play uh I sing
I sing
[Music]
I sing oh
oh oh
I sing figure I figure I figure I figure
I figure I figure out
wow yeah uh I have to get back to you on
that
so I'm trying to ask everybody this what
is your favorite animal hmm tiger shark
best kind of shock I'm partial to
scorpions
I like those really big dogs the ones
they use the word of bears oh Siberian
tiger whichever is strongest
I'm also fond of Starlings is there a
kind of dingo that is also a shark
scolopendra gigantia the Black Widow
humans I suppose yeah
Triceratops really
take a guess
that's German for squirrel ants they
build marvelous structures and cooperate
when threatened I find them
inspirational
identify if it's a noble rhinoceros I
don't see why it's relevant but
leopard seal I love those deep sea
animals like the big fin squid
dragonflies
such perfect creatures Roberts the huge
ones I envy ads
for their Clarity of purpose uh yeah I
can see it
all right let's hear that fighting
spirit
[Music]
ah
that's exactly what I'm talking about
who can one know that one knows nothing
can a single grain of sand differentiate
between Heap and not Heap if the
universe is a simulation why aren't
there more elephant seals
it Thrills me to put aside my
preparations and humor your brilliant
inquiries doctor it Thrills me kind
words thank you
you've been rather quiet today doctor
I've gotten a lot done
if one built a violin of Planck length
could one play music into another
universe
someone must build a particle collider
around the Sun
I wonder if frogs dream of Pawns
can a fish that never sees the surface
no it's underwater
there it goes
I was just in the kitchen anyone have
something they want to confess
those banana peels are not mine I ain't
a snitch but let's just say those corn
dogs are gone for good I was just trying
to make a milkshake I saw someone steal
leftovers but I'm afraid to say who it
is not my fault your kitchenware melts
so easily oh
papa is there anything you'd like to say
to our teammates I'm looking forward to
working with you likewise it will be a
pleasure and I with you how gracious of
you yes well let's get this done
anyone want to hear my favorite joke
about the periodic table no thank you
can't say I do I'm guessing no yeah I'm
still puzzling over the last one
uh I do not this is not perhaps the best
time I do not
cause you want that table broken over
your head no no one wants that no uh
Winston please no no
nope
anyone want to hear my favorite joke
about the periodic table nah nah nah
nah n a i don't know will it make me go
hey hey
yes but I can't promise I'll understand
it
here's another one what sickness do
pilots usually get sick of your jokes oh
Asic hmm
what the flu okay Winston
I'm glad that's impossible for me
what was your function before the crisis
the day before the crisis what did you
do you know before was a crisis I
collected payments at a laser tag arena
I was a lifeguard at a water park I
served coffee I drove a tractor I
massaged sheep on a free-range pasture
really wait for real seriously
is it true really
is that true could that be he won't tell
me either
I don't think so but he wouldn't tell me
either